euroseek.com 2017-12-16

# Euroseek.com - Trusted Web Directory Since 1996 @ the First European Web Directory, Euroseek.com

This statement is intended to clarify our commitment to protecting your privacy, as well to be sure that you are comfortable with the steps we have taken to provide a satisfactory experience in using the EuroSeek directory. This statement explains our current information gathering process, which is subject to change without notice. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time to update yourself on any such changes.

This Privacy Policy extends to:

  * Any personally identifiable information collected by EuroSeek.
  * How such information is used by EuroSeek.
  * You choices with regard to the collection, use, and distribution of that information.
  * The security procedures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of any such information under EuroSeek's control.
  * How to correct any errors in such information.

**_Collection and Use of Information_**

**Registration:**  In order to submit a site, users must first complete our registration form. During this process, users are required to provide contact information, including their name and email address. This information is used to contact users about the services on our site in which they have expressed interest.

**Payment:** When a registered user is submitting a site to EuroSeek's directory, information is required on the submission form. Users must provide contact information (name, email, and billing address), and financial information (such as credit card numbers and expiration dates). This information is used for billing purposes, and to contact the user in the event a submission cannot be processed. 

**_Information Use_**

**User Profiles:** We retain the information collected through log files and via the information users provide during registration and site submission, in order to create profiles.  These profiles are stored data that we maintain on individual users detailing their characteristics. As a result, collected information is tied to users' personally identifiable information in order to improve our customer service and provide offers. _User profiles are not shared with third parties._

**Log Files:** As with most website servers, EuroSeek uses log files. These files include IP (internet protocol) addresses, ISP (internet service provider) information, browser identification, platform identification, referring and/or exit pages, time/date stamps, and the number of clicks. These logs are used to analyze browsing trends, track users' movements in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and administer the site. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**_Communications from EuroSeek_**

**Updates and Special Offers:**  Registered users will occasionally receive information on services, products or special deals, though all users have the option not to receive these types of communications.

**Service Announcements:** On rare occasions, for example, if our service is temporarily unavailable, it may be necessary to send service-related announcements, generally in the form of email. As these communications are not promotional in nature, users are generally not allowed to opt-out of them.

**Customer   Service: **We maintain regular communication with users in order to provide requested services, or in regard to any account-related issues. These are handled by email or phone, in accordance with the individual user's wishes.

**_Information Sharing_**

**Disclaimer:** While EuroSeek makes every effort to protect user privacy, we may be required by law to disclose information when we have a good-faith belief that such information is necessary in order to be in compliance with a court order, legal process or current judicial proceeding involving our website.

**Aggregate (Non-personally Identifiable Information):** We share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers and partners.  This information includes page views, browser types, unique visitors, and additional broad demographic data. This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Third-Party Advertisers:** EuroSeek shares site usage data about its users with reputable third-party advertisers. While we make every effort to accept only advertisers who are reputable, and who share our commitment to privacy protection, we cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of any advertiser, promotional link, sponsor, or any other third party. Users are advised to check the individual privacy policies for any third-party sites they may visit.

**_Situations where EuroSeek Will Share Users' Personal Information:_**

**Third-Party Intermediaries:** EuroSeek uses an external credit card processing company to bill users for services. Such companies do not retain, store, share, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

This statement is intended to clarify our commitment to protecting your privacy, as well to be sure that you are comfortable with the steps we have taken to provide a satisfactory experience in using the EuroSeek directory. This statement explains our current information gathering process, which is subject to change without notice. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time to update yourself on any such changes.

This Privacy Policy extends to:

  * Any personally identifiable information collected by EuroSeek.
  * How such information is used by EuroSeek.
  * You choices with regard to the collection, use, and distribution of that information.
  * The security procedures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of any such information under EuroSeek's control.
  * How to correct any errors in such information.

**_Collection and Use of Information_**

**Registration:**  In order to submit a site, users must first complete our registration form. During this process, users are required to provide contact information, including their name and email address. This information is used to contact users about the services on our site in which they have expressed interest.

**Payment:** When a registered user is submitting a site to EuroSeek's directory, information is required on the submission form. Users must provide contact information (name, email, and billing address), and financial information (such as credit card numbers and expiration dates). This information is used for billing purposes, and to contact the user in the event a submission cannot be processed. 

**_Information Use_**

**User Profiles:** We retain the information collected through log files and via the information users provide during registration and site submission, in order to create profiles.  These profiles are stored data that we maintain on individual users detailing their characteristics. As a result, collected information is tied to users' personally identifiable information in order to improve our customer service and provide offers. _User profiles are not shared with third parties._

**Log Files:** As with most website servers, EuroSeek uses log files. These files include IP (internet protocol) addresses, ISP (internet service provider) information, browser identification, platform identification, referring and/or exit pages, time/date stamps, and the number of clicks. These logs are used to analyze browsing trends, track users' movements in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and administer the site. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**_Communications from EuroSeek_**

**Updates and Special Offers:**  Registered users will occasionally receive information on services, products or special deals, though all users have the option not to receive these types of communications.

**Service Announcements:** On rare occasions, for example, if our service is temporarily unavailable, it may be necessary to send service-related announcements, generally in the form of email. As these communications are not promotional in nature, users are generally not allowed to opt-out of them.

**Customer   Service: **We maintain regular communication with users in order to provide requested services, or in regard to any account-related issues. These are handled by email or phone, in accordance with the individual user's wishes.

**_Information Sharing_**

**Disclaimer:** While EuroSeek makes every effort to protect user privacy, we may be required by law to disclose information when we have a good-faith belief that such information is necessary in order to be in compliance with a court order, legal process or current judicial proceeding involving our website.

**Aggregate (Non-personally Identifiable Information):** We share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers and partners.  This information includes page views, browser types, unique visitors, and additional broad demographic data. This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Third-Party Advertisers:** EuroSeek shares site usage data about its users with reputable third-party advertisers. While we make every effort to accept only advertisers who are reputable, and who share our commitment to privacy protection, we cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of any advertiser, promotional link, sponsor, or any other third party. Users are advised to check the individual privacy policies for any third-party sites they may visit.

**_Situations where EuroSeek Will Share Users' Personal Information:_**

**Third-Party Intermediaries:** EuroSeek uses an external credit card processing company to bill users for services. Such companies do not retain, store, share, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Business Transitions:**  In the event EuroSeek becomes involved in a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users personal information will be part of the assets transferred in most instances. Should this occur, users will be notified via a prominent notice on our website for thirty (30) days prior to any change of ownership or control of their personal data. If, as a result of the transition, users' personally identifiable information will be used in a different manner than that specified at the time of collection, they will be given choices consistent with our notification of changes policy.

**Choice/Opt-Out:** Users who no longer wish to receive promotional communications my opt-out of receiving these communications by sending email to [[info@euroseek.com]](mail:info@euroseek.com) with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line.

**_External Links_**

EuroSeek contains links to external websites. Please be aware that EuroSeek is not responsible for the privacy policies of these external sites. We advise all users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**_Security_**

EuroSeek takes every possible precaution to protect our users' personally identifiable information. When users submit sensitive data via our site, their information is protected both on- and off-line.

Sensitive information collected via our registration/submission forms is encrypted using SSL, but we also do everything in our power to protect user-data off-line. All user information is restricted in our offices, and only employees who need the information in order to perform specific tasks are granted access to it. As well, all employees are frequently reminded about the importance of maintaining user privacy, and kept up to date about our privacy policy.

**_Notice of Change_**

In the event EuroSeek changes its privacy policy those changes will posted to this privacy statement, as well as any other places on our site that we deem appropriate, so that we can ensure our users are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it may be disclosed. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy in force at the time the information was collected.

If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that which was outlined at the time of collection, users will be notified via email. Users will be given a choice as to whether or not their information will be used in this different manner. Users who have opted out of all communication with EuroSeek, or who have deactivated or deleted their accounts will not be contacted, nor will their information be used in this new manner. 

If we make material changes to our privacy policy that do _not_ affect  already-stored user information we will post a prominent notice on our site notifying users of the change. In some cases, users may be contacted by email as well.

**Choice/Opt-Out:** Users who no longer wish to receive promotional communications my opt-out of receiving these communications by sending email to [[info@euroseek.com]](mail:info@euroseek.com) with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line.

**_External Links_**

EuroSeek contains links to external websites. Please be aware that EuroSeek is not responsible for the privacy policies of these external sites. We advise all users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**_Security_**

EuroSeek takes every possible precaution to protect our users' personally identifiable information. When users submit sensitive data via our site, their information is protected both on- and off-line.

Sensitive information collected via our registration/submission forms is encrypted using SSL, but we also do everything in our power to protect user-data off-line. All user information is restricted in our offices, and only employees who need the information in order to perform specific tasks are granted access to it. As well, all employees are frequently reminded about the importance of maintaining user privacy, and kept up to date about our privacy policy.

**_Notice of Change_**

In the event EuroSeek changes its privacy policy those changes will posted to this privacy statement, as well as any other places on our site that we deem appropriate, so that we can ensure our users are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it may be disclosed. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy in force at the time the information was collected.

If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that which was outlined at the time of collection, users will be notified via email. Users will be given a choice as to whether or not their information will be used in this different manner. Users who have opted out of all communication with EuroSeek, or who have deactivated or deleted their accounts will not be contacted, nor will their information be used in this new manner. 

If we make material changes to our privacy policy that do _not_ affect  already-stored user information we will post a prominent notice on our site notifying users of the change. In some cases, users may be contacted by email as well.
